dslextreme.com 2010-12-30

# DSL Extreme - Privacy Policy

**Quick Return:** Terms of Service > Privacy Policy

DSL Extreme is committed to protecting the privacy and security of the information provided by customers visiting our Web site or using our services. DSL Extreme may request information from people visiting our Web sites or using our services. DSL Extreme is the sole owner of the information collected. **DSL Extreme respects your privacy and will not knowingly distribute or cause to be distributed your personal information to any entity for any reason.** We will not collect any personally identifiable information unless the visitor/customer provides it to us voluntarily. Personally identifiable information includes a visitors/customer’s name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. DSL Extreme is dedicated to building a long-term relationship with all of our customers and visitors. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

**Prequalification and Service Quotes:** In some cases, a visitor may be required to complete a prequalification or inquiry form to order a product or to receive certain information. During the registration process, the visitor is required to give specific information such as name and e-mail address, mailing address, location and phone number. This information is used to pre-qualify and contact the visitor regarding services offered by DSL Extreme for which the visitor has expressed interest.

**Ordering:** When taking orders online, DSL Extreme will request certain information from a customer to complete an order. The customer's information will include name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, payment information and other information as may be requested by DSL Extreme in the order form. This information is used for billing purposes, fulfillment of orders, ongoing account maintenance and upgrades.

**Security:** When customers are asked to enter certain sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected through a Secure Socket Layer (SSL). SSL negotiates and employs the essential functions of mutual authentication, data encryption and data integrity for secure transactions. While on a secure page, such as an order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer® and Netscape Navigator® becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are viewing other Web sites.

All customer/visitor information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted to DSL Extreme developers, network operations personnel and other qualified employees (such as billing clerks or customer care representatives). Finally, the servers on which DSL Extreme stores personally identifiable information are kept in a secure location.

**Cookies:** A "Cookie" is a piece of information that is sent from a DSL Extreme Web server to a visitor's browser and stored on the visitor's hard drive. DSL Extreme uses Cookies when a visitor orders a product or registers for a specific program. The Cookie stores information that allows DSL Extreme Web sites to remember a visitor the next time he or she visits a particular DSL Extreme Web site. Cookies also allow us to tailor our Web sites to better match visitors' interests and preferences. Visitors may choose to disable Cookies by changing their browser settings; however, they may not be able to access some of the information on our Web sites.

**Links:** DSL Extreme Web sites contain links to other Web sites. DSL Extreme is not responsible for the privacy practices of these Web sites. We encourage our visitors and customers to read the privacy policy of each Web site they visit. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on DSL Extreme Web sites.

**Sharing:** DSL Extreme may partner with other parties to provide specific services, such as billing solutions, which are designed to enhance the functionality of our products and services. When a customer signs up for these services, DSL Extreme will only share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.

**Special Cases:** It is DSL Extreme’s policy not to use or share the personal information about visitors or customers in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, DSL Extreme may disclose personal information about visitors or customers, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies; to operate the services properly; or to protect DSL Extreme and our customers.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:** If a customer needs to update or change personal identification information, DSL Extreme will help the customer to correct, update or remove personal data provided to DSL Extreme. The customer can update or change personally identifiable information using the Account Manager on our website <http://www.dslextreme.com/access/> or by contacting our customer service department at 800-774-3379.

**Responses to Email Inquiries:** When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to DSL Extreme, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. DSL Extreme does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

**Notification of Changes:** If we make any changes to the DSL Extreme Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on DSL Extreme Web sites so customers/visitors are informed. We will always use information in accordance with the DSL Extreme Privacy Policy.

**Questions:** Any questions or comments regarding privacy should be sent to [support@dslextreme.com](mailto:support@dslextreme.com) or mailed to:   
**  
Customer Service**  
DSL Extreme  
21540 Plummer Street - Suite A  
Chatsworth CA, 91311
